OpenClaw x Binance AI Agent
Chinese Voiceover Demo · 2 Minutes
Turn AI ideas into runnable plans, docs and assets.
What Problems It Solves
1) Too many ideas, no clear priority
2) Product and engineering are hard to align
3) No standard demo assets for showcase
How It Works
$ bash scripts/setup_binance_ai_agent.sh
$ bash scripts/run_demo.sh
Auto-generate answers: innovation + KPI + 2-week MVP
Output Assets
• docs/demo_latest.md
• docs/showcase.md
• docs/assets/demo-cn-2min.mp4
• docs/assets/demo-cn-voice.mp3
Feature Optimization Done
• Prompt list is now configurable by file
• One-click full build pipeline
• Chinese TTS + 120s video auto composition
Business Value
1) Shorten idea-to-delivery cycle
2) Unify product / engineering / data communication
3) Build reusable demo assets for team and clients
OpenClaw Binance AI Agent
GitHub: hwl66/openclaw-binance-ai-agent